<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Yosemite on TobyTime</title><link>https://tobytime.club/tags/yosemite/</link><description>Recent content in Yosemite on TobyTime</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright © 2023 TobyTime |</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tobytime.club/tags/yosemite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dog-Friendly Yosemite: Day 2</title><link>https://tobytime.club/blog/yosemite-day-two/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tobytime.club/blog/yosemite-day-two/</guid><description>On the second day of our trip to Yosemite National Park, Toby and I opted for a more tranquil and less crowded experience, away from the bustling Yosemite Village. We wanted to take it easy after an eventful first day. We began with a peaceful stroll along the scenic Wawona Meadow Loop trail, immersing ourselves in the serene beauty of the surroundings. Later, we embarked on a drive up to Glacier Point, making a stop at Washburn Point along the way to capture the breathtaking views.</description></item><item><title>Dog-Friendly Yosemite: Day 1</title><link>https://tobytime.club/blog/yosemite-day-one/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tobytime.club/blog/yosemite-day-one/</guid><description>Our day began with capturing breathtaking moments at Tunnel View, where the grandeur of Yosemite unfolded before our eyes. Eager to explore further, we ventured into the valley and embarked on a delightful walk through Cook&amp;rsquo;s Meadow, leading us to the enchanting trail of Lower Yosemite Falls. After a lunch at Village Grill, we concluded this eventful day with a leisurely stroll to the lower loop of Mirror Lake.
Tunnel View Leaving the cabin, we set off, heading north along the windy Wawona Road.</description></item><item><title>Dog-Friendly Itinerary to Yosemite</title><link>https://tobytime.club/blog/yosemite-itinerary/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tobytime.club/blog/yosemite-itinerary/</guid><description>Yosemite National Park is a captivating wilderness that beckons nature enthusiasts from around the world. With its awe-inspiring granite cliffs, iconic waterfalls, ancient sequoia groves, and diverse wildlife, Yosemite is a testament to the raw beauty of the natural world.
While most areas of Yosemite National Park have restrictions on dogs, there are still opportunities for you and your furry companion to explore and enjoy the natural wonders together. Let us guide you on a journey that showcases the dog-friendly side of Yosemite, so you can create your own unforgettable memories with your furry companions in this breathtaking wilderness.</description></item></channel></rss>