<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>California on TobyTime</title><link>https://tobytime.club/en/tags/california/</link><description>Recent content in California on TobyTime</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright © 2023 TobyTime |</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tobytime.club/en/tags/california/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Point Vicente in Rancho Palos Verdes</title><link>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/point-vicente-rancho-palos-verdes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/point-vicente-rancho-palos-verdes/</guid><description>Rancho Palos Verdes, a scenic coastal city just south of Torrance, offers a slice of paradise with its stunning golf courses and trails along the Pacific Ocean. The best part? These trails are pup-approved, making it an ideal spot to treat your furry friend to a sensory adventure while you soak up the California sun on a leisurely stroll.
Our Journey at Point Vicente On a beautiful Saturday afternoon, Toby and I decided to explore the beautiful trail near the Point Vicente Interpretive Center.</description></item><item><title>California</title><link>https://tobytime.club/en/destinations/california/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tobytime.club/en/destinations/california/</guid><description>Our Spots Check out the map below to see all the awesome places Toby and I have explored in California so far. It&amp;rsquo;s like our treasure map of beautiful parks and dog-friendly spots! Just click on the picture to open an interactive map in Google Maps, and you can start planning your own adventure-filled trips.
Related Blogs If you want to dive into the details of our escapades in each of these spots, be sure to explore these blog posts!</description></item><item><title>Dog-Friendly Hike at the Will Rogers State Park</title><link>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/will-rogers-state-park/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/will-rogers-state-park/</guid><description>The Will Rogers Historic State Park is a stunning ranch once owned by the popular Hollywood actor in the 1920s-1930s, Will Rogers. This remarkable estate has been graciously donated to California State Parks following his death, offering visitors a chance to immerse themselves in its timeless allure. With an array of hiking trails to choose from, including some that connect to the adjoining Topanga State Park, Toby and I eagerly embarked on our exploration on the scenic Inspiration Loop Trail, a delightful dirt path that welcomes our furry companions on a leash.</description></item><item><title>First Sandy Walk at the Venice Beach</title><link>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/venice-beach/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/venice-beach/</guid><description>Calling all beach lovers! Venice Beach is a must-visit destination in southern California that you simply can&amp;rsquo;t miss. And guess what? I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist the opportunity for Toby to get his paws in the sandy shores for the first time.
Dog-Friendly Breakfast Spot Our day at Venice Beach started with a delightful breakfast at none other than the famous Eggslut. Despite the lack of outdoor seating, the staff at Eggslut warmly welcomed Toby and me inside the restaurant.</description></item><item><title>Quiet and Challenging: Franklin Canyon</title><link>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/quiet-challenging-franklin-canyon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/quiet-challenging-franklin-canyon/</guid><description>Franklin Canyon is an expansive park within the beautiful Beverly Hills landscape with an abundance of picnic areas and scenic trails. It&amp;rsquo;s a haven for hiking enthusiasts, catering to those with a moderate level of fitness and a love for outdoor exploration.
Directions to the Hastain Trail Explore the Franklin Canyon Hastain Trail, located at the southern edge of the vast Franklin Canyon. Accessible from Santa Monica Blvd or Sunset Blvd, head north on North Beverly Dr until it splits into Franklin Canyon Dr.</description></item><item><title>Coffee and Stroll: UCLA Botanical Garden</title><link>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/coffe-stroll-ucla-botanical-garden/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/coffe-stroll-ucla-botanical-garden/</guid><description>The UCLA Botanical Garden is a hidden gem nestled within the vibrant campus of the University of California, Los Angeles. This enchanting garden offers a serene escape from the bustling city, with its diverse collection of plants and tranquil pathways.
Dog-Friendly Coffee Shop Venture beyond the usual Starbucks corners in Westwood Village, and discover the world of cozy coffee shops. When searching for a dog-friendly spot, Toby and I stumbled upon Espresso Profeta, which has an outdoor area where we could sit in the sunshine together.</description></item><item><title>Picnic and Pictures: Griffith Park</title><link>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/picnic-picture-griffith-park/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/picnic-picture-griffith-park/</guid><description>Griffith Park is an iconic park in Los Angeles with an extensive network of trails, perfect for hiking, walking, and exploring with your furry companion. From the stunning views of the Hollywood Sign to the serene tranquility of the Griffith Observatory, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone to enjoy. Plus, there is no entrance fee!
Entrance &amp;amp; Parking One option is the main entrance on Los Feliz Blvd, marked by the iconic bear statue.</description></item><item><title>Dog-Friendly Walks Near West Holllywood</title><link>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/dog-friendly-walks-west-hollywood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/dog-friendly-walks-west-hollywood/</guid><description>Join Toby and me as we explore the wonders of Los Angeles, venturing within a 10-mile radius of West Hollywood, to discover our top three favorite spots.
Picnic and Pictures: Griffith Park Griffith Park, nestled in the heart of Los Angeles, is an iconic park with a network of trails that are just perfect for leisurely strolls and exploration alongside your furry companion. As you wander along the park&amp;rsquo;s trails, prepare to be captivated by breathtaking vistas, including the world-famous Hollywood Sign and the Griffith Observatory.</description></item><item><title>Dog Trip to Santa Barbara</title><link>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/santa-barbara/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/santa-barbara/</guid><description>Santa Barbara is a charming coastal city, just a short two-hour drive north from Los Angeles. We spent a day visiting three beautiful dog-friendly spots to enjoy the city&amp;rsquo;s natural beauty and southern California&amp;rsquo;s delightful February weather.
MacKenzie Dog Park Eager to let Toby stretch his legs leash-free after our lengthy drive to Santa Barbara, we first headed to the MacKenzie Dog Park. While dedicated parking wasn&amp;rsquo;t readily available, luck was on our side as we found street parking on State Street.</description></item><item><title>Dog-Friendly Trail of Crystal Cove</title><link>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/crystal-cove/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tobytime.club/en/blog/crystal-cove/</guid><description>Immerse yourself in the natural beauty of Crystal Cove State Park in Newport Beach. Its dog-friendly paved trail along miles of Pacific coastline is a perfect place for an afternoon walk with your furry companion.
Directions to the Dog-Friendly Trail While many trails in Crystal Cove State Park unfortunately don&amp;rsquo;t welcome our furry friends, there&amp;rsquo;s a ray of sunshine for dog owners – the dog-friendly paved Crystal Cove Trail by Pelican Point!</description></item></channel></rss>